Enhance Armament!
Oh, my God.
Kirito, Kirito, say something, Kirito!
Let's go!
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
I'd like to see the way I'm learning.
I'm going to connect
you to the way you buy.
You're the way I hear you.
I'm going to the same way you can't.
I'm going to go myself.
Oh...
Kirito!
Come on, wake up!
System call.
Generate luminous element.
Transfer human unit durability.
Self to lift.
Don't die.
That's enough, Eugeo.
I think I'll be okay now.
Whoa, take it easy.
You were hurt pretty bad.
You might have internal wounds
my healing didn't catch.
It's not as bad as when
those goblins beat me down.
Anyway, I'm worried about her. What?
Who cares?
She tried to kill you, remember?
I know what you said before, about
letting hate get the better of me.
She was just doing her duty.
She wasn't fighting for revenge
or because she hated us.
I get that.
Still, that's no excuse.
I can't forgive the church
or the Integrity Knights.
They have all this power, but
they're just a bunch of hypocrites.
If they really wanted to
protect humanity, they could.
They'd rather protect a lie instead.
I know what you mean, but you can't
forget these knights are human, too.
They got their own problems, like
how this one felt about her gender.
I gotta say, your perfect
weapon control art's awesome.
Those knights didn't
stand a chance against it.
This fight's over.
There's no reason to hate Fanatio
and the Four Whirling Blades anymore.
So let it go.
They're human.
Yeah, you're right.
I understood that much
about her during the fight.
She fought with heart like us.
I guess that's why she was so powerful.
You're right about that.
It's all a matter of perspective
when you think about it.
The knights see themselves as
good while you see them as evil.
But the reality is, you,
me, and these knights,
we're all human at the end of the day.
So who's to say who's good and who's bad?
Crap, almost forgot.
Could you give those two knuckleheads
some of that antidote for me?
Don't forget to snap their
daggers before you do.
Oh, and make sure they're
not packing any other tricks.
What about Administrator Kirito?
Will you be as understanding
of her as you are her knights?
System call!
Generate luminous element!
What's wrong?
I can't stop the bleeding.
Help me! Alright.
This isn't working.
She's lost way too much blood.
But I can't just let her die like this.
She's lived a hundred years
worrying, loving, suffering.
She was alive.
I can't let her soul get erased.
Help us.
This night's dying.
I know there's more of
you out there. Come on.
One of you needs help.
Can anyone hear me?
A priest, a monk, anyone?
She's dying.
Help her. Please.
You can't let her die.
That's it.
What do you think you're doing?
You're supposed to use
that on Administrator!
Yeah, I know!
But if I use it on her, I can save her.
This tagger's her only hope.
I can save her with it!
I have to use it!
Goodness gracious, you
really are something!
Cardinal, she needs help.
I'm sorry, I know I shouldn't have.
I know what's happened, and
please, don't apologize.
I will heal Fanatio Synthesis 2. However,
I will have to bring her to me as it will
take some time to
initiate a full recovery.
These potions
will heal you now.
As far as I can tell, administrator
is not yet in her waking state.
If you can make it to the
top floor before she wakes,
you can still eliminate her
without the use of the dagger.
Hurry!
Only a few
integrity knights remain.
I kind of lost it there, sorry.
No, you don't ever have to apologize.
Hey, did you get that?
Cardinal said something weird just now.
Something about
Administrator's waking state.
Perhaps she spends most
of her time sleeping.
Cardinal said administrator
and some of her
knights have been around
for a couple of centuries.
So who knows what kind
of strain that puts on
him maybe it's part of
the deal administrator
Has to sleep all day to stay alive well i
guess we'll find out once we get up there.
What the heck is this?
Watch out!
Something's coming!
Thank you for waiting.
Which floor would you like to visit?
Which floor?
Do you mean you can take us
to any of the floors above?
Um, we're fugitives, and we sort
of like broke into the cathedral.
Isn't your Elevate, I mean, floating
thing off-limits to folks like us?
I'm not sure what you mean.
Anyone who wishes to use
this platform may do so.
My job is to merely
operate it, nothing more.
Okay.
We'll take you up on your offer, then.
Hey, wait!
Are you sure it's safe?
Of course.
Besides, there's no more stairs to climb.
Yeah, but...
Never mind.
All right, please take
us up as high as you can.
Right away, sir.
System call.
Generate aerial element.
Burst element.
So, uh, have you been
doing this for a while now?
As a matter of fact, I have.
For 107 years, actually.
107 years?
And this is all you do day in and
day out? Not quite. I get breaks.
I'm allowed to take one
at noon to have my lunch.
And then at night, I get
to sleep, so there's that.
That's not quite what I mean.
Um, what's your name?
My name.
I seem to have forgotten it.
That makes sense.
Operator is all anyone calls me anymore.
I think we can help.
We, um, we came here to bring
down the head of the church,
the one who forced this calling onto you.
You don't say.
If the church is gone, you'll
be released from your calling.
You'll be free to do whatever you want.
Is that so?
I'm at a loss.
I don't know anything of the
world outside this shaft.
Therefore, I have no idea what
new calling I would choose.
Although, if I could wish
for anything else to do...
I wish I could fly this platform
outside and go wherever I wanted.
Thank you for your patience.
This is the 80th floor,
the Cloudtop Garden.
I didn't think anything in this world
could be more boring than my calling,
but it's nothing compared to hers.
I could look forward to
growing old and retiring.
She's stuck with hers forever.
Cardinal said that even if you stopped
a person from aging with the sacred art,
there's no way to stop
their soul from aging.
Little by little, their memory crumbles,
and in the end, it falls apart.
The Axiom Church is straight-up evil.
We're the only ones who can stop
Administrator and free everyone.
It's a start.
But that's not the end
of this world's problems.
The real challenge is what comes after.
I thought after we defeated Administrator,
Cardinal would make things right again.
Won't she?
Sort of.
We can talk about it after
we get Alice back. Okay.
Oh, amazing.
Alice!
Please wait.
I want to let her soak in the sun.
Not for long.
A few more moments will do.
Let me do the fighting, okay?
Be ready with the dagger.
That's the only way
you're gonna get her back.
I'll block her strikes with my
body if it comes down to it.
But can't we...
Look, there's no other way.
I'll charge Alice, take
the hit and pin her down.
Then you stick her with
the dagger. Got it?
Sorry.
Nah, don't worry about it.
If this works, you can pay me back later.
I can't tell if she's
got her sword or not.
It doesn't matter.
We'll get to her before she can finish
casting her perfect weapon control.
But we gotta attack now, because the more
we wait, the more time she has to cast it.
You're right.
And if she does finish casting it,
I think I can use mine two more
times before I have to restore it.
And that's our backup plan.
I can only use mine one more time.
And we still got to deal with the
commander of the knights after Alice.
Come on, let's do this.
Against all odds, you two have
made it all the way up here.
I anticipated your escape from the prison.
But I did not anticipate
what happened next.
Eldrie should have caught you.
Yet you defeated him.
Then Deo Selbert.
I have no idea how.
And then, you defeated Fanatio as well.
And now you have set foot here.
It is shocking.
Where do you get the power
to overcome such knights?
Why do you wish to disrupt the order here?
Explain yourselves.
Very well.
I will get answers with my blade.
No way.
Damn it! Her sword!
It's already in perfect control.
Why did you not draw your swords?
If you were mocking me, know this.
I intentionally held back on that
strike just now as a warning.
The next one shall eliminate
your lives entirely.
For the honor of the knights you've
defeated, I insist you attack me in earnest.
System call.
Please accept our humble apologies.
We didn't mean to disrespect you just now.
My name is Kirito.
I'm a swordsman in training, and I
wish to duel with you, Lady Alice.
Very well.
Let us see just how wicked you are,
by the quality of your swordsmanship.
Before we start this up,
I got a question for you.
If that tree we saw just now is your
sword, that means it's its true form.
So how can a tree that
small be so powerful?
Long ago, the spot where the central
cathedral stands was the Place of Beginnings,
a place which Stacia,
the goddess of creation,
gifted to humanity.
In the center of a tiny village,
there was a beautiful spring.
On its banks, there grew
a single osmanthus tree.
This weapon, the osmanthus
blade, was forged from it.
A tree created by the
goddess reincarnated.
The oldest thing in existence,
a divine weapon indeed.
Everlasting eternity is its attribute.
A single petal can split stone
or tear the ground asunder.
You don't say.
That's a great score.
It's this world's first
indestructible object.
Thanks for sharing, but we
should get back to business now.
All right.
Integrity Knight Alice.
If you're ready, on guard!
You are the second person to
withstand my attacks for this long.
Your will and dedication are apparent.
They brought you this far.
However, the church is far
greater than your will,
and I will not allow you to disturb
the peace of this realm any longer.
Farewell, human.
Enhance Arminet!
Oh, my God.
That was amusing, and quite futile.
Mere ice cannot withstand my flowers.
I shall fight you next, so be
patient and wait your turn.
Enhance argument!
He went for my sword!
Now, Luchio!
Kirito...
Alice...
No!
Kirito!
Alice!
Aaah…
Thank you so much for watching.
Everything turns to dust to
And everything turns to dust to dust
no one to die Don't
forget me no one to die
Don't forget me no one
to die Next time Truce